- Ahhhhhhhh.
- All right, keep it out.
Are you guys looking at it?
Do you see this? Look at that.
Okay, Freddie, pull back.
And that answers
our viewer's request which was, "will you please show me
My tongue appreciates
your interest.
- Okay,
till the next "iCarly"... - Play us out, Freddie.
Baby, will you take me back?
there I said it
I said it, I said it
baby, will you take me too?
well, there I said it
I said it, I said it
and we're clear.
Good show, you guys.
- Thanks.
- We know.
- I'm all tired.
- Me too. I need a bath.
- Ewww, don't take a bath,
take a shower. - What's wrong
You sit there
in your own wet dirt.
- Gross.
- Yeah.
- Awww, no, come on.
- What's the matter?
Gibby forwarded me
one of those annoying chain letter e-mails.
Oh yeah, the one
about the ghost girl named consuela
- Yeah.
- I got it this morning.
- Me too.
- Better forward it.
Yeah, you gotta send it
to 20 people or else you'll have bad luck.
- Consuela's revenge.
I'm not forwarding
the stupid e-mail.
You better.
It said the last person who didn't forward it,
Yeah, he was just running
on his little wheel and then pffffft.
Yeah, pffffft.
Okay, no hamster went pffffft.
I don't believe in it,
so I'm not doing it. Delete.
Okay, but when you get
butt warts, don't come cryin' to us.
Don't worry.
- Oh, my God. A spider.
- Where? There on your cheek.
And your bad luck begins.
- Ha-ha.
- I'm not kidding.
- Dude, there really is
a spider. - Right under your eye.
- Yes.
- Well, get it off.
- Okay, okay, uh...
- Just grab it.
- Ooh, I can't,
I can't, I can't. - I'll get it. I'll get it.
Just be careful.
Carly, carly,
wait till you see what I found.
I gotta go.
Okay, love you too.
- What is that?
- A pak-rat machine.
- Pak-rat?
- Yeah, it's a really old video game from, like,
I've played
versions of it online, but this is the original
One of the most popular
video games of all time.
- Cool. You think it'll work?
- I don't know.
I gotta check out all the wiring
and circuit boards and stuff.
- But shouldn't you be working
on your labradoodle sculpture? - I got time.
That doctor's not coming
to get it till Sunday. Hey, did you look him up online?
Yeah, his brother
owns seven art galleries in Seattle and Vancouver.
- So make him happy.
- No worries.
I'm gonna build him
the best labradoodle in the history
This thing must have been
in that junk yard for years.
- How can you tell?
- Well, I don't think this is supposed to be in there.
- Hold it.
- No.
Too slow, buddy.
Eat it, eat it, eat the cheese.
Carly, doorbell!
You couldn't get the door?
It's right there.
Okay, I'll get the door.
Hey, I thought you were Freddie.
If anyone else said
that to me, I'd punch 'em in the mouth.
Sorry.
He just called and said he needs to borrow
- Yeah, I don't care.
- What are you doing here?
Ah, my mom told me
I couldn't leave the house till I clean up my room,
so I locked my door,
snuck out the window, and took a bus here.
You got any meat?
- Just go home
and clean up your room. - Will you come help me?
- Uh.
- Come on.
Okay.
Hey, Spencer,
will you drive me and Sam over to her house?
Sure, just lemme finish
this game.
Oh.
Did you see that?
Eat the cheese, eat the cheese.
- What's he playing?
- Pak-rat. Some video game
- Fredward Benson.
- Mom, would you...
- Freddie, lets go.
- Mom, calm down.
You got the tennis racket?
- Yeah, one sec.
- Uh, what up with your little pink shorts?
They were white,
but somehow a red sock got in our washing machine
- Wow, that sounds
like some pretty bad luck. - It's consuela's revenge.
No, it was just
a laundry mishap.
- Okay.
- Whatever you say.
Yeah.
Another 10,000 points,
another extra rat. I am supreme.
- Is that an old
pak-rat machine? - Yeah, he found it
- Freddie, let's go.
- I'm coming. Bye.
- Later.
- See ya, pink pants.
- Carly, would you gimme
a bite of my sandwich? - You are kidding me.
Come on, I'm starving.
- Thank you.
- You gonna drive us or not?
- Spencer, Spencer,
are you gonna drive us to Sam's or not?
Ahhh, that was close.
A little bang-bang
to the chitty chitty.
I am good.
I'll call a cab.
Hey.
- What's up?
- You gotta see this video some kid sent in to "iCarly."
- Ooh, is it good?
- Good?
The guy can pull his lower lip
down over his chin.
- Ewww, gross. Show me.
- 'Kay.
Gonna go full frame on this.
You are gonna die when you see how this guy...
- smoke.
- Whoa.
- Why's it smoking?
- I don't know. Maybe it's got a...
- it's consuela's revenge.
- Aah.
Sam and I told you
you'd have bad luck if you didn't forward
- This has nothing to do
with consuela. - Yes, it does.
I'm not leaving this room
until you... I'm going downstairs.
Carly...
listen, computers
have technical problems all the time.
- Yeah, but they don't explode.
- It didn't explode...
you've been cursed
by consuela 'cause you're too stubborn
- It's not that I'm stubborn...
- Just forward the e-mail.
Hold me tighter.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- What's that stuff?
- Parts for my labradoodle sculpture.
Finally.
Wait, doesn't that rich guy
want the sculpture by Sunday?
- Yeah.
- And you haven't even started it yet?
- I've been busy
playing pak-rat. - Busy.
- Hey what's this?
- Bag of dog hair.
Oh...
- where'd you get
a bag of dog hair? - I stopped
- Shampoodles?
- Uh-huh.
- Hey, is this
your high score? - Yup.
- 867,000.
- Uh-huh.
How long did it take you
to score that high?
Well, I started playing
last night at around 11:00 and finished at maybe 6:00 A.M.?
- You played pak-rat
for seven hours straight? - Yeah, why?
What happened
when you had to pee?
- Oh, see, I took
this plastic bottle and taped it to my ankle,
Hey.
Hey, look at this.
The highest score on record
for a single game of pak-rat was achieved by a girl
- Yeah, I've heard
of Sasha striker. - Yeah.
It says when she was only 16,
she became the number one pak-rat player in the world.
Then she disappeared
and no one's seen her since.
- Really?
- Weird.
Whoa.
She scored 1,034,000 points in one game.
Not bad for a lady rat.
- I bet
you could beat her score. - Don't encourage him.
- I gotta beat that score.
- After you finish the labradoodle sculpture.
- Just a quick game.
- That doctor guy's coming to pick it up tomorrow.
- It'll be ready. One game.
- At least start on the sculpture first?
Tail's done.
Yes.
- Spencer. Wake up.
- What happened?
- Did you play
pak-rat all night? - I don't know. Why?
Why is there a bagel
in your pants?
- I got hungry and then I...
- Come with me.
What about
the labradoodle sculpture for that important doctor guy?
- He's not picking it up
till Sunday. - Today is Sunday.
- It is?
- Yes. You have a problem. You're addicted to pak-rat.
I am not.
- Admit it.
- No, I am not addicted to pak-rat.
- Would ya stop...
I'm addicted to pak-rat. - I know.
- I can't believe this.
You promised me my labradoodle sculpture
- I know.
- He's really sorry.
- Do you know
how much influence I have in the Seattle art community?
And what is that on your face?
It's smoked salmon.
What is wrong with you?
- Look, I...
I got a little obsessed with pak-rat.
- Yeah, ya wanna play?
- No.
- Spencer.
- I'm sorry. Listen. Is today your wife's
- No, it's next Saturday, why?
- If you'll just give me till then...
- oh.
-... I promise, I swear, I will make you the best
- He'll get it done.
- I will see you 9:00, Saturday morning.
- Wow, that was almost
really bad. - Yeah.
Well...
I can't believe
you're still playing that.
And now my finger smells
like smoked salmon.
- Gary wolf is so gorgeous.
- Why does he have to be a senior?
A hot, hot senior.
- Hi.
- What happened to you?
I was riding my bike
down corbin boulevard on my way to school
- On corbin?
- Uh-huh.
A bus ran over my lunch.
Well, "flat"
doesn't mean "inedible."
- I'm telling you,
it's consuela's revenge. - There's no such thing
Yeah, keep thinkin' that.
You guys, what am I gonna do
about Spencer?
He's gonna ruin his whole life
if I don't get him to quit playing
- And it's your fault.
- How's it my fault?
- You had to go look up
Sasha striker. - Who's Sasha striker?
- The best pak-rat player
of all time. - Come on, Spencer'll get sick
No way.
This isn't about him loving pak-rat.
It's this, this crazy
competitive thing with him.
So let's go find
this Sasha striker chick. Maybe Spencer can beat her.
- Can't.
- She like dropped off the face of the earth years ago.
Well, come on,
there's gotta be some way we can find the woman.
So, come on, "iCarly" fans...
there are hundreds
of thousands of you guys all over the country.
- All over the world.
- One of you has to know where Sasha striker is.
- And if you help us
locate her... - Or get her to contact us
-... you'll win
these fabulous prizes. - This $25 gift certificate
This survival knife
that used to belong to my grandmother.
And an autographed photo
of a man who got pregnant.
- So, come on, "iCarly fans."
Help us find Sasha striker. - If you like
- and survival knives...
- And pregnant dudes.
- She's here.
- She's comin' up the elevator.
Sweet.
Hey, hey, uncool, uncool.
- Just stop playing
for a minute. - No.
I did what you asked me to do.
I shaved, I took a shower, I mailed that movie
who's the girl
in the sexy purple tank-top?
- Her name is Sasha.
- Sasha striker.
- The number one pak-rat player
in the world. - How did you guys find her?
- Through the power
of "iCarly." - Now just play Sasha
Yeah.
I hear you're really good.
So why don't you beat me?
- Oh, you don't think I can,
do you? - I know you can't.
You know, I feel scared
and attracted to you at the same time.
Are you guys gonna make out
or play some pak-rat?
Who's here?
- Hey, hey.
Who are you guys? - I'm Barry schatz
- Why are you here?
- 'Cause we heard Sasha striker was gonna be here...
-... to defend
her pak-rat title. - This is big.
This is Barry schatz
from the video game channel, live in Seattle,
where Sasha striker,
the number one pak-rat player in the world,
- uh, Spencer shay.
If there's any girl out there
who wants to go out with me, any girl at all...
- well, I guess
we're gonna do this. - I guess we are.
- It could take a long time.
- I got time.
Do you have a boyfriend?
- How long
have they been playing? - Six hours.
Kill me.
- And Sasha striker
finishes with a total of 1,322,000 points.
Now, Spencer shay
has only one rat left to beat that score
Good luck.
You'll need it.
Look out.
Will Spencer shay
hold up under this pressure? Will he be able to...
stop watching
the video game channel, ya big bunch of losers.
Get a job, kiss a girl,
do something. No offense.
It's incredible.
Spencer shay is less than 400 points away
You don't have to be pretty.
All I'm looking for is someone female
come on, Spencer.
It happened.
It happened right here in Seattle.
Spencer shay has defeated
the great Sasha striker and he is now the number one...
bye.
Okay, later.
Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
Get out.
- Well.
You're the real deal. Nice game.
- Wanna go for a ride?
- I would love to.
But this is all I can give you
right now.
- Call me.
- We'll see.
Okay.
A rich doctor's gonna be here in nine hours
Who wants to stay up all night
and help me build it?
I'll give you each $20.
- Whatever.
- Okay.
So, what do you think?
I like it.
But it's my wife's opinion
that matters.
Honey?
Happy Birthday.
She likes it.
- Hey, did you get an e-vite
to Karen Franklin's party? - Yeah.
- I didn't.
- Well, maybe 'cause you always call her
So?
I still like to party.
Oh, man, I got another one
of those chain letter e-mails from gibby.
Well, forward it
so you won't have all kinds of bad luck like Freddie.
- Ah, Freddie didn't have
any bad luck. - What are you talking about?
I did all that stuff.
- What?
Wait, his bike falling apart? - I loosened some bolts.
- His laptop smoking?
- Shorted out the battery.
- The pink shorts?
- One red sock in his washing machine.
- Okay, what about the spider
on his face? - That was just lucky.
No way...
- what?
- Gary wolf.
- What about Gary wolf?
- He's texting me.
He wants me to meet him
at the crown Ridge mall.
- But he's a senior.
- I know.
Why would the hottest senior
in our school ask you to meet him at the mall?
I mean, not that you're not cool
and appealing and everything, but why you?
I don't know.
But bye.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- I gotta tell you something.
- You're gonna tell me that there was no bad luck?
That Sam did all that stuff
to me?
- How do you know?
- Well, I didn't know when it was my pink shorts
but I saw her loosening
the bolts on my bike.
- But I thought
your bike fell apart while you were riding it?
I just pretended on that one.
- So you're not gonna try
to get her back? - You mean,
like send her
a fake text message that looks like it came
telling her to meet him
at the crown Ridge mall?
- I didn't know
you could be so bad.
- Good night.
- Night.
- Carly, Carls, hey...
- Hmm?
- Did you play
pak-rat all night? - Mm-hmm.
It's so fun.
Yeah, all right, kiddo.
Go on up to bed.
Carry me.
It's such a fun game.
Sync by hana.Bean www.Addic7ed.Com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0